export default function getData() {
    return [
        {
            question: "Are you sensitive to others?",
            a: "yes",
            b: "no",
            correct: "a",
        },
        {
            question: "Do you have a tolerance for conflict?",
            a: "no",
            b: "yes",
            correct: "b",
        },
        {
            question: "Do you adapt well to change?",
            a: "yes",
            b: "no",
            correct: "a",
        },
        {
            question: "Do you set limits to your ideas?",
            a: "no",
            b: "yes",
            correct: "a",
        },        {
            question: "Do you invest time in improving your skills?",
            a: "no",
            b: "yes",
            correct: "b",
        },
        {
            question: "Do you manage your habits well?",
            a: "yes",
            b: "no",
            correct: "a",
        },        {
            question: "Are you persistent?",
            a: "yes",
            b: "no",
            correct: "a",
        },
        {
            question: "Do you give up when you don't achieve your goals?",
            a: "no",
            b: "yes",
            correct: "a",
        },        {
            question: "Are you accountable to yourself?",
            a: "no",
            b: "yes",
            correct: "b",
        },
        {
            question: "Are you able to get your message across?",
            a: "no",
            b: "yes",
            correct: "b",
        },  
        {
            question: "Do you have a solid belief system?",
            a: "yes",
            b: "no",
            correct: "a",
        },
    ];
}
